# Eriberto Remigio

#### **Profile**



#### Contact Info

20 Lindsay Street, Invermay TAS 7248
Mobile: +61 0401 249 224
Offshore address:
126 Purok 2, Dela Paz Norte
City of San Fernando, Pampanga, Philippines 2000
Overseas Mobile: +63 09182 61 5191

Email: jrem7@yahoo.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

As an experienced IT Professional, I look forward to furthering my career within the area of Software/Web Development (MVC/ASP.NET Core), COBOL (Mainframe) Programming, Level 2 IT Support (Remote) or basic Systems Administration work (Remote). I have been residing overseas (Philippines) since 2021 and prefer working remotely/offshore if available.

#### SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Information Communication Technology & Networking
  - Desktop and laptop technical support (onsite and remote)
  - Use of ServiceNow platform for logging service tickets
  - Windows Server 2012 R2, Novell Netware, Director, Virtual VMWare, Virtual Box
  - Domain Controllers, Active Directory, DHCP, DNS, WDS, SCCM
  - Manage users, groups & organisational unit accounts within networks
  - Provide security & backup on entire network
  - Mapping shared network drives
  - TeamViewer, MS Remote Assistance, Remote monitoring & administration
  - Installation, troubleshooting & maintenance of user software & hardware
  - Microsoft Office 365 products technical support
  - Operating Systems: Windows XP/7/8/10; Ubuntu (Linux); Mac OS
- Application and Web Development
  - Visual Studio 2022. MS SQL/MYSQL.
  - Bootsrap 5, CSS
  - ASP.NET Core 6.0, C# ASP.Net MVC 5, CSS, Web API
  - Visual Basic 6, VBA. VB .NET/ASP/HTML
  - Git/Github tool for application development
  - WORDPRESS, COBOL, BASIC, Dbase 3+/Clipper
  - Macromedia Dreamweaver MX, Flash MX, Fireworks MX. Adobe Photoshop, Acrobat

#### **EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS**

Certificate III & IV in Information Technology — MS Systems Administration, Windows 2000 Server

2003

GippsTAFE Central Gippsland Institute of TAFE, Newborough VIC

Music Teacher's Diploma (Major in Guitar) - partial

1992

PWU University, Manila, Philippines

Integrated Hotel and Restaurant Services  Jimmy Valeros Consultancy & Training - Midland Plaza Hotel, Manila, Philippines	1990
Computer Programming in Business Systems/ Advanced COBOL Programming Systems Technology Institute, Makati City, Philippines	1985
Bach. of Science (Elec. & Comms. Eng.) — partial University of Santo Tomas, Manila, Philippines	1984
High School Graduate University of Santo Tomas, Manila, Philippines	1983
Supplemental Courses:	
Complete C# ASP.NET MVC 5 Course Online Udemy Online Course, Instructor — Mosh Hamedani	2018
Audio-Video Products Servicing/Consumer Electronics PROSKILLS Technical Training Center Corporation — Pampanga Philippines	2012

#### EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

# IT Support/Remote Technical Support (Level 2)

2019-21

Goanna Solutions, 100 Harris Street, Pyrmont NSW 2009

Level 2 IT Onsite TAS/Remote Tech support (**IBM Australia**) – servicing various onsite and remote tech support (level 2) for Westpac Bank Australia clients.

IT Support 2018

Ignite Services, Level 9, 1 York Street, Sydney NSW 2000

IT technical support – deployment and installation of client desktop computers at Launceston TAS region (Casual employment).

#### IT Support / Deployment Engineer

2018

# Muscatech, PO Box 4044 Keilor Downs 3038

Deployment, upgrade and installation of client desktop computers at Launceston, Burnie and Devonport TAS region (Casual employment).

#### Entrepreneur | Internet Café

2008-16

#### Asgard Internet Café, Dela Paz Norte, CSFP, Philippines

➤ Performed Managerial & Supervisory tasks on all operations of small proprietary business, including customer service, sales, IT technical support & maintenance roles (assembly/disassembly of PCs, troubleshooting, repairs of peripherals/PCs, installation & upgrading of software/hardware).

### Support Officer/ASIC-2

2002-06

#### Australian Securities & Investments Commission (ASIC), Traralgon, VIC Australia 3844

Gained valuable experience with a federal Government organisation. Commenced as a casual and upgraded to a permanent role. Duties included customer service, document processing, call center roles, preparing managerial reports (daily, weekly, monthly, annually & adhoc). Developed VBA applications for staff & management use. I had to leave ASIC in 2006 to become a full time carer for my mother who suffered from Parkinson's disease with Alzheimer.

#### Systems Administrator / Developer

2001-02

#### Greater Gippsland Petroleum, Traralgon, VIC Australia 3844

Administered & maintained POS systems (on-site & off-site) within the Gippsland region comprising 9 Shell Petrol stations. Provided technical support for staff, developed applications in VB6/VBA, extraction (download) of data from POS systems into (upload) the IBM AS400 mainframe. Daily backups, Novell Netware administration & generated various reports for management. Company was bought by Shell (Melbourne) hence jobs were made redundant by 2002.

#### Computer Programmer

1999-00

#### Parabolic Builders Inc., Makati City, Philippines

Developed payroll & financial applications for construction company, ran weekly payroll reports of workers & weekly reports for management. I solely designed & coded Payroll system in dBase3+.

#### Computer Programmer

1994-99

#### RODA Traders Inc., Makati City, Philippines

Programming Architectural Design and Interior Renovation systems. I was in charge of developing their Payroll System & provided maintenance for all PCs & computer devices. Generated weekly worker payroll reports, wrote contract proposals & adhoc reports.

#### Freelance Programmer / Developer

1987-94

Various clients, Philippines

Developed experience & knowledge in IT industry. Developed programming skills in different code languages. Learnt hardware assembly/ disassembly, troubleshooting & preventive maintenance. Developed business applications: Payroll, Project Monitoring, Cash Flow & Inventory.

#### **Associate Programmer**

1985-87

#### Systems Resources Inc., Makati City, Philippines

Undertook robust training in IT while liaising with company clients, including international banks, health care, tyre Industries in US and worldwide. Developed programs using PC, mini computers & mainframes, particularly IBMs. Used computer languages: COBOL, Dbase3+ (compiled in Clipper), MS BASIC. Conducted coding, testing & documented programs.

#### REFERENCES

#### Mr. Michael Simnett - IT Manager

Australian Head Office IBM Australia Ltd Level 17 259 George Street Sydney NSW 2000

Phone: 0421 610 457

Email: msimnett@au1.ibm.com

#### Mr. Eyal Sternberg -Program Manager

IMI Solutions 9 Subway Road Rockdale NSW 2216 Phone: 0423 132 822

Email: eyal@imi.solutions

# Mr. Chris Beven — Job Provider Consultant CVGT Australia Ltd Launceston

Level 2 87 George Street Launceston, TAS 7250

Page 3

Phone: 03 54407646 Email: cbeven@cvgt.com.au

## Mr. Brendan Hofer — IT Manager Muscatech

PO Box 4044 Keilor Downs 3038

Phone: 0410 997 237

Email: bhofer@muscatech.com.au

# Ms. Mukti/Mr. Nishant Dewangan — Resourcing Consultant Ignite Services

Level 9, 1 York Street, Sydney NSW 2000 Phone: 02 9250 8000 & 02 9250 8018

Email: Mukti@igniteservices.com